<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NextVanProto</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="terms_conditions">
        Welcome to NextVan! By using our app, you agree to our terms:
        \n\n1. You must use our service lawfully.
        \n2. We are not responsible for lost or stolen items.
        \n3. Booking fees are non-refundable.
        \n4. Data privacy is important to us. See our Privacy Policy for more details.
        \n\nBy clicking OK, you agree to these terms.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">
        We respect your privacy. Your data is securely stored and never shared with third parties without your consent.

        \n\n1. **Data Collection:** We collect personal data such as name, contact details, and booking history to enhance your experience.

        \n2. **Data Usage:** Your data is used for booking management, customer support, and service improvements.

        \n3. **Data Protection:** We implement strict security measures to safeguard your information.

        \n4. **Third-Party Sharing:** We do not share your personal data with third parties except when required by law or to provide essential services.

        \n5. **User Rights:** You can request data deletion or modification at any time through our support team.

        \n6. **Cookies and Tracking:** We may use cookies to improve app performance and personalize your experience.

        \n\nBy using NextVan, you agree to our Privacy Policy.
    </string>

    <string name="help_center">
        Welcome to the Help Centre! Here are answers to common questions:

        \n1. **How do I book a ride?**
        Open the app, enter your departure and destination, and select an available ride.

        \n2. **How can I cancel my booking?**
        Go to "My Bookings," select your trip, and choose "Cancel."

        \n3. **How do I contact support?**
        Email us at support@nextvan.com or call our hotline.

        \nNeed further assistance? Contact our support team anytime!
    </string>




</resources>